[
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_074",
        "question": "A 47-year-old otherwise healthy woman presents to the clinic with several concerns. <br>- Over the past several months, she has experienced thickening of her skin around her hands, forearms, and face. <br>- Her fingers turn blue and then pale when she is exposed to cold. <br>- Additional recent symptoms include fatigue and gastroesophageal reflux. <br>- She takes no medications and has no family history of autoimmune disease. <br>- On physical examination, the patient has skin thickening on the hands, forearms, and face. <br>- She also has hypopigmented macules on the hands and lower legs.",
        "option1": "Morphea",
        "option2": "Stiff-skin syndrome",
        "option3": "Scleredema",
        "option4": "Systemic sclerosis",
        "correct_option": 3,
        "ai_prediction": 3,
        "ai_confidence": "61%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_105",
        "question": "A 67-year-old male presents with unrelenting itch present over the last 6 months. <br>- He endorses weight loss and fatigue. <br>- He denies any liver or kidney disease. <br>- He denies exacerbation of itch with water. <br>- A KOH scraping is performed which is negative for scabies. <br>- Physical examination is significant for numerous punctate and linear erosions consistent with excoriations as well as diffuse shoddy lymphadenopathy.",
        "option1": "Renal pruritus",
        "option2": "Hodgkin lymphoma",
        "option3": "Scabies",
        "option4": "Cholestatic pruritus",
        "correct_option": 4,
        "ai_prediction": 1,
        "ai_confidence": "67%",
        "ai_is_correct": false
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_031",
        "question": "The patient is a 19-year-old woman who presents with several years of a worsening rash. <br>- The rash appears as erythematous, hyperkeratotic thin plaques in a seborrheic distribution. <br>- The patient states that the rash is very irritating and sometimes pruritic. <br>- The patient’s main complaint is that the rash exudes a malodor. <br>- The patient states that her father has a similar rash that he chooses not to treat.",
        "option1": "Epidermodysplasia verruciformis",
        "option2": "Grover disease",
        "option3": "Darier disease",
        "option4": "Hailey-Hailey disease",
        "correct_option": 3,
        "ai_prediction": 3,
        "ai_confidence": "40%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_048",
        "question": "A 62-year-old man with well-controlled rosacea, a monoclonal gammopathy of undetermined significance, and chronic lymphocytic leukemia (CLL; stable on no current therapy) was seen in the clinic for a full-body skin check. <br>- Results of his examination were unremarkable except for the presence of periorbital, yellow-brown plaques with violaceous borders involving the upper and lower eyelids, bilaterally. <br>- There was induration, but no warmth or tenderness, of the periorbital plaques. <br>- He first noticed these lesions around the time he was diagnosed with CLL; initially they were more discrete yellow papules that developed into plaques over time. <br>- They are completely asymptomatic.",
        "option1": "Adult-onset xanthogranuloma",
        "option2": "Necrobiotic xanthogranuloma",
        "option3": "Adult-onset asthma with periocular xanthogranuloma",
        "option4": "Erdheim-Chester disease",
        "correct_option": 2,
        "ai_prediction": 2,
        "ai_confidence": "66%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_111",
        "question": "A 60-year-old female presents with a non-healing painful ulcer on her right leg for 4 months. <br>- She says she first noticed it after she accidentally bumped into a chair. <br>- She is known for rheumatoid arthritis and hypertension, and has taken methotrexate and bisoprolol for years. <br>- According to the patient, oral antibiotics and wound debridement have only increase the size of the ulcer. <br>- Physical exam reveals a 5x5 cm fibrinous ulcer with violaceous undermined borders on her right shin.",
        "option1": "Venous ulcer",
        "option2": "Pyoderma grangrenosum",
        "option3": "Traumatic wound",
        "option4": "Arterial ulcer",
        "correct_option": 4,
        "ai_prediction": 3,
        "ai_confidence": "89%",
        "ai_is_correct": false
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_113",
        "question": "A 12-year-old female presents with hemorrhagic crusts on the lips and erosions of the oral, genital, and conjunctival mucosa for 2 days. <br>- According to the parents, there was a pneumonia outbreak at school. <br>- The patient also had a high fever and cough a week before the onset of cutaneous lesions. <br>- The parents deny any new medication and a history of allergies. <br>- The physical exam reveals no other skin findings.",
        "option1": "Herpetic gingivostomatitis",
        "option2": "Mycoplasma pneumoniae-induced rash and mucositis",
        "option3": "Stevens-Johnson Syndrome",
        "option4": "Erythema multiforme major",
        "correct_option": 4,
        "ai_prediction": 4,
        "ai_confidence": "85%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_097",
        "question": "A 48-year-old white man presents to the dermatology clinic with papulosquamous cutaneous lesions that recently appeared on his chest, arms, and the dorsal aspects of his hands. <br>- The patient has a family history of autoimmune disorders, including systemic lupus erythematosus (SLE). <br>- Physical examination reveals that the lesions lack induration and do not appear to be leaving scars. <br>- Biopsy of the lesion is performed, revealing mild inflammatory infiltrate. <br>- Direct immunofluorescence shows a granular deposition at the dermal-epidermal junction. <br>- Serology indicates that the patient is positive for anti-Ro/SSA (Sjögren-syndrome-related antigen A).",
        "option1": "Photolichenoid drug eruption",
        "option2": "Subacute cutaneous lupus erythematosus",
        "option3": "Discoid lupus erythematosus",
        "option4": "Pemphigus foliaceus",
        "correct_option": 4,
        "ai_prediction": 2,
        "ai_confidence": "44%",
        "ai_is_correct": false
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_056",
        "question": "A 7-month-old male who had been born prematurely presents with a 2-month history of diarrhea, failure to thrive, alopecia, and rash involving the perioral, perianal, and acral areas. <br>- He had been treated unsuccessfully for presumed atopic dermatitis with topical corticosteroids. <br>- He was exclusively breastfed until 2 months ago, when he was transitioned to formula. <br>- Examination reveals an irritable, thin infant with sharply demarcated red, inflamed, scaly plaques and erosions around his mouth, anus, eyes, hands, and feet. <br>- Diffuse hair loss is noted on the scalp, eyebrows, and eyelashes. <br>- Paronychia and nail dystrophy are noted on his upper and lower extremities.",
        "option1": "Atopic dermatitis",
        "option2": "Acrodermatitis enteropathica",
        "option3": "Acrodermatitis enteropathica-like eruption (AELE)",
        "option4": "AELE unrelated to zinc deficiency",
        "correct_option": 2,
        "ai_prediction": 2,
        "ai_confidence": "56%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_030",
        "question": "The patient is a 38-year-old Hispanic woman who presents with a 1-year history of a very pruritic rash over her interscapular area. <br>- On examination, she has a circular area of slightly hyperpigmented macules in the interscapular region. <br>- The patient complains of pruritus but no pain in the area of the rash. <br>- The patient has no other medical problems and has no systemic symptoms. <br>- She has no relevant social or family history and does not take any medications.",
        "option1": "Macular amyloidosis",
        "option2": "Prurigo nodularis",
        "option3": "Lichen amyloidosis",
        "option4": "Paresthetica",
        "correct_option": 1,
        "ai_prediction": 1,
        "ai_confidence": "75%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_055",
        "question": "A 50-year-old woman presents with a 5-day history of progressive, painful rash involving her face, trunk, extremities, nasal tip, and ears, in addition to fever and arthralgia. <br>- She admits to a history of polysubstance use and states that her last use was a week prior to symptom onset. <br>- She denies a history of autoimmune disease or recent travel. <br>- Examination reveals retiform purpura with areas of necrosis and bullae formation. <br>- Urine toxicology screening is positive for cocaine, and laboratory findings include leukopenia and an elevated erythrocyte sedimentation rate (70 mm/h).",
        "option1": "Warfarin-induced skin necrosis",
        "option2": "Levamisole-induced antineutrophil cytoplasmic antibody vasculitis",
        "option3": "Tinea incognito",
        "option4": "Disseminated intravascular coagulation",
        "correct_option": 4,
        "ai_prediction": 4,
        "ai_confidence": "77%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_139",
        "question": "A 22-year-old female presents with a brown rough spot on the left shin which she noted when shaving her leg. <br>- She thinks it may have been there for a few weeks. <br>- She denies any pain, pruritus, or spontaneous bleeding from the site. <br>- She cannot recall any trauma that may have caused the lesion. <br>-  She denies any personal or family history of skin cancer. <br>-   Physical exam reveals a thin, firm brown dome shaped papule on the left shin that invaginates upon pinching.",
        "option1": "Dermatofibroma",
        "option2": "Keratoacanthoma",
        "option3": "Fibrous papule",
        "option4": "Keratosis pilaris",
        "correct_option": 2,
        "ai_prediction": 4,
        "ai_confidence": "54%",
        "ai_is_correct": false
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_066",
        "question": "A man, aged 42 years, presents with a 6-month history of a painful, scaly skin rash. <br>- The eruption is symmetrically distributed over photosensitive areas, affecting his face, neck, upper back, forearms, and hands. <br>- The dorsal surfaces of his hands and forearms exhibit a dusky brown coloration over rough and cracked skin. <br>- He complains of itching and burning and reports intermittent vomiting and diarrhea. <br>- He admits to heavy alcohol intake for the last 2 decades and denies taking any medications. <br>- Neuropsychiatric evaluation reveals short-term memory loss, speech problems, and poor concentration.",
        "option1": "Polymorphous light eruption",
        "option2": "Pellagra",
        "option3": "Phototoxic skin reaction",
        "option4": "Photoallergic skin reaction",
        "correct_option": 1,
        "ai_prediction": 1,
        "ai_confidence": "73%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_091",
        "question": "A 45-year-old woman presents with enlarging blood vessels on her tongue that recently have increased in size and number. <br>- Numerous 1- to 2-mm discrete red macules and papules are seen on her tongue, oral mucosa, nose, lower lip, and fingertips. <br>- She has had frequent nosebleeds since childhood as well as iron-deficiency anemia that has not responded to iron supplementation. <br>- Her father, who died at the age of 50, had similar symptoms.",
        "option1": "Vascular hemorrhage",
        "option2": "Hereditary hemorrhagic telangiectasia",
        "option3": "Bloom syndrome",
        "option4": "Ataxia-telangiectasia",
        "correct_option": 3,
        "ai_prediction": 4,
        "ai_confidence": "53%",
        "ai_is_correct": false
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_138",
        "question": "A 34-year-old woman presents with complaints of a severely itchy rash affecting both lower legs that developed three days ago after returning from camping six days ago. <br>- She reports during the camping trip they often hiked for several hours a day, and she wore shorts due to the humid, hot weather. <br>- When the rash began, it began as small red bumps that formed larger fluid filled bumps. <br>- She has tried over the counter cortisone that helps with the itch a little bit. <br>- She denies any new topical lotions, laundry detergents, or body washes. <br>-   Physical exam reveals multiple streaks of yellow vesicles on bright pink erythematous bases in a linear distribution on the bilateral lower extremities.",
        "option1": "Poison ivy allergic contact dermatitis",
        "option2": "Irritant contact dermatitis",
        "option3": "Nummular eczema",
        "option4": "Scabies",
        "correct_option": 2,
        "ai_prediction": 2,
        "ai_confidence": "89%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_132",
        "question": "A 45-year-old man presents to the primary care clinic with a red, itchy rash on the eyebrows and around the nose that has been ongoing for eight months. <br>- He has tried moisturizers to the areas, but the flakiness returns a few days later. <br>- He also reports he has dandruff in his scalp. <br>- He denies any new facial products or using any other creams or lotions. <br>-   Physical examination reveals greasy yellow scale on poorly demarcated erythematous patches on the eyebrows and bilateral nasal alar creases. <br>- Mild white scale is appreciated diffusely across the scalp.",
        "option1": "Rosacea",
        "option2": "Psoriasis",
        "option3": "Acne vulgaris",
        "option4": "Seborrheic dermatitis",
        "correct_option": 2,
        "ai_prediction": 2,
        "ai_confidence": "74%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    }
]